What happened with Leslie?
Why did she dump you?
(Howard:)I don't know. She just said,
"Howard, Mama's a rolling stone."
(Howard:)Then her call waiting beeped,
and she was gone.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
(Sheldon:)If you were in a non-emotional
relationship...
(Sheldon:)...then why are you having
what appears to be an emotional response?
(Raj:)Sheldon,
he obviously had feelings for her.
(Howard:)Of course I had feelings for her.
I saw her naked for God's sake.
Okay, look,
you just need to get your mind off it.
Do you wanna go to the comic-book store,
maybe see a movie?
I don't wanna go anywhere.
(Sheldon:)You know...
(Sheldon:)...I'm given to understand
that there's an entire city in Nevada...
(Sheldon:)...designed specifically to help people
like Howard forget their problems.
We can replace them
with new problems such as alcoholism...
(Sheldon:)...gambling addiction
and sexually-transmitted diseases.